Holiday House is a comedy, drama film directed by Alex Heller.
A content creator feels obligated to let her
internet benefactor visit her workshop.
Shelley, played by AnnaSophia Robb.
Markie, played by David Brown.
Matt, played by Antonio Marziale.
Mom, played by Adrienne Becker.
The Holiday is a 2006 American romantic comedy film
written and directed by Nancy Meyers.
Co-produced by Meyers and Bruce A.
Block, the film was shot in both California and England.
It stars Cameron Diaz and Kate Winslet as Amanda and Iris, two lovelorn women from opposite sides of the Atlantic
Ocean, who arrange a home exchange to escape heartbreak during the Christmas and holiday season.
Jude Law and Jack Black play the film's leading men Graham and Miles, with Eli
Wallach, Edward Burns, and Rufus Sewell playing supporting roles.
The Holiday premiered in New York City on November 29, 2006, before it was
released theatrically in the United States on December 8, 2006.
It was distributed by Sony Pictures Releasing in the United States and
Canada and by United International Pictures overseas.
The film was a box office success, grossing $205.8 million
worldwide against a production budget of $85 million.
It received generally mixed reviews from critics upon release, with praise for its visual
design and the performances of the cast, but criticism for its predictable plot.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.